{
    "subject": "resource/Oceans_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Oceans",
    "human_readable": "The name of the film is 'Oceans'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8123751878738403,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Oceans'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7864102125167847,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film 'Oceans' about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7803483605384827,
            "question": "Is 'Oceans' a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7672612071037292,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Oceans'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6067713499069214,
            "question": "Where was the film 'Oceans' set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5868279933929443,
            "question": "Was the film 'Oceans' a commercial success?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5412436127662659,
            "question": "What year was the film 'Oceans' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5160764455795288,
            "question": "Who are some of the main actors in the film 'Oceans'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4156018793582916,
            "question": "What is the name of the film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4106908440589905,
            "question": "Are there any sequels or spin-offs to the film 'Oceans'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of the film is 'Oceans'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5634_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5634_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of the main actors in the film 'Oceans'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5634_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film 'Oceans' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5634_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5634_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5634_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5634_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5634_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5634_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5634_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5634_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5634_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5634_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5634_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's my evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention \"Oceans\" multiple times as the title of a French nature documentary film, directed and produced by Jacques Perrin. Therefore, according to the provided context information, the statement that the name of the film is 'Oceans' is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}